http://www.multiplication.com/help/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY - Multiplication.com Policy Effective Date: April 30, 2018Welcome to Multiplication.com, the website and online service owned by IXL Learning, Inc.  Multiplication.com is a teacher-created website designed to help kids learn the math facts.  We provide games, activities, and quizzes for kids to use under the guidance of their teachers and parents.  Multiplication.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared.  We appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully. This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use posted on our website, sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of Multiplication.com.  Your use of Multiplication.com is conditioned on your acceptance of this policy.INFORMATION WE COLLECTMultiplication.com's goals in collecting information are to provide you with a customized experience and a high level of technical support.Personally Identifiable InformationSome personal information is gathered when you register. Depending on your account type, Multiplication.com may ask for your name, e-mail address, birthdate and/or additional information. We may also ask you to choose a username and password.In addition to the information we collect when you register, we may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you contact our technical support team. We also collect information about your use of Multiplication.com and any information that you submit to Multiplication.com, such as answers to questions, tests, or quizzes.Furthermore, when you send e-mail, user surveys, or other communication to Multiplication.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.Additionally, in some instances, a game may request that a user provide a name (e.g., to identify a particular player in a multi-player game). In those instances, the name is not collected by us.Non-personally Identifiable InformationOur definition of non-personal information is any information that does not personally identify you.Non-personal information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous.Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about your connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.HOW WE USE INFORMATION COLLECTEDInformation you submit to us is generally used to carry out your requests, process orders, respond to your inquiries, better serve you or in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information.  When you are on Multiplication.com and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Multiplication.com, unless it is specifically stated otherwise.  We may use information collected to provide feedback to the user and educational institution and for compiling reports and awards. From time to time, we may also use your information to communicate with you or to provide promotional emails about our service or about other products and services we think you may enjoy. We send marketing and promotional emails only to Parent and Teacher users, and not to children or students.HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION COLLECTEDMultiplication.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties except when we have your permission or under specific circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. The following describes some of the circumstances under which your information may be disclosed.As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets.  If Multiplication.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, your personal information may be transferred to the purchaser.  If another entity acquires us or all (or substantially all) of our assets, the personally identifiable information and non-personal information we have about you will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity, provided the successor entity is subject to the same commitments for the previously collected student information.  No personal information will be transferred in the event of a merger or sale unless the recipient has committed to the Student Privacy Pledge principles.Multiplication.com may disclose information collected from users associated with an educational institution with other users designated by the educational institution, such as teachers and school administrators of that institution.Multiplication.com may disclose information to our trusted vendors, third party service providers and individuals for the purpose of providing services or products for us or on our behalf, which could include analytics, hosting, billing, advertising and marketing.We may also disclose information to other businesses and brands within our common ownership and control, including IXL Learning and any other company or brand owned by IXL.HOW WE COLLECT AND USE NON-PERSONAL INFORMATIONLike most websites and online services, we and our vendors automatically collect usage information when you visit our Website, read our emails, or otherwise engage with us. This information is typically collected through a variety of tracking technologies, including cookies, web beacons, Flash objects, log files, and similar technology (collectively, “tracking technologies”). These tracking technologies collect information about your visit to the website (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click), information about your browser and online usage patterns (e.g., Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, pages viewed, whether you opened an email , links clicked), and information about the device(s) you use to access the website (e.g., mobile device identifier, mobile carrier, device type, model and manufacturer, mobile device operating system brand and model, and whether you access the site from multiple devices). We may collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the website and to understand more about the demographics of our users. Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our users, we are unable to respond to Do Not Track signals set by your browser at this time. We do not permit third parties to collect information from our website for the purpose of sending targeted advertisements on our site or on other websites.We use or may use the data collected through tracking technologies to better display our website, to save you time, to provide better technical support, for promotional purposes, and to track website usage. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services (particularly those that require you to sign-in) may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.HOW TO UPDATE, CORRECT, OR DELETE PERSONAL INFORMATIONYou may edit your account information at any time by logging into your account and clicking the “Settings” link. We recommend that you review your personal information periodically to ensure that it is accurate, complete, and current.If you have forgotten your password, you may request a new one by choosing “Settings – Reset My Password” or by contacting support@multiplication.com. A new password will be sent to the e-mail address you specified during registration. For all other problems logging into Multiplication.com services, please contact our technical support team using the contact information at the end of this policy.Please contact technical support for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your account for any Multiplication.com service. Residual information may remain within our archive records, such as for billing and tax purposes.HOW WE PROTECT CHILDREN’S PRIVACYMultiplication.com accounts are created by parents and educational institutions. Multiplication.com does not permit children under the age of 13 to create an account and does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from children under the age of 13 without the consent of a parent or educational institution.Multiplication.com will not ask children under age 13 for more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity.If you are a Parent, you may provide consent for your child’s registration by first registering yourself on Multiplication.com. Once registered, you will receive an email requesting your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information about your child.  After providing your consent, you can create a restricted account for your child, monitor the data on your child’s account, or revoke a child’s permission to use Multiplication.com by deleting the account.Alternatively, your child can be registered to use Multiplication.com through his or her school. The school’s ability to consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information is limited to the educational context where an operator, such as Multiplication.com, collects personal information from students for the use and benefit of the school, and no other commercial purpose.PARENT RIGHTSParents have the right to review and request that Multiplication.com delete any Personal Information collected and retained about their child. If you would like to request that Multiplication.com delete any Personal Information we may have about your child, or to request that we stop the further collection or use of your or your child's personal information, please contact Multiplication.com at: privacy@multiplication.com or you may complete the child account deletion form at: https://www.multiplication.com/delete-account. If your child is using the website through a Teacher account, we may refer your request to the Teacher.KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECUREMultiplication.com takes reasonable and appropriate measures to protect the security, privacy, confidentiality, and integrity of information under our control.  We also take reasonable and appropriate steps to only release Children’s Personal Information, if any, to service providers and third parties who are capable of and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality and security of that information.For your protection, remember to log out of all accounts before closing your browser. There is a log out link available on most Multiplication.com pages. After logging out, make sure to close all browser windows. This is to insure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a public computer.We restrict access to personal information to Multiplication.com employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our products and services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.DATA RETENTIONWe will retain personal information for as long as needed for the purpose of providing the Service and for our internal business purposes, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. For example, we may retain certain data as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for recordkeeping or other legitimate business purposes, or if required by law. We may also retain information which has been de-identified or aggregated such that it can no longer reasonably identify a particular individual. All retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Multiplication.com does not retain student personal information associated with Teacher Accounts for longer than necessary to deliver to services for which it was collected.  Information will be deleted using reasonable measures to protect against its unauthorized access or use.CONSENT TO TRANSFER INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATESMultiplication.com is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States.  By using Multiplication.com, you consent to the collection, transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESPlease note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If there are significant changes to this policy or in how Multiplication.com uses your personal information, we will notify you about them by placing a prominent notice on our website or by e-mail.  If required, we will also seek a parent or teacher’s prior consent to these changes. Parents and Teachers will also be notified of any changes when they login to their account. By continuing to use Multiplication.com services after that time, you agree to the revised Privacy Policy.If you have a question regarding this statement, or if a question was not addressed in this privacy policy, you may contact technical support using the contact information below. We will do our best to answer your question promptly and accurately.OTHERMultiplication.com may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services, or your use of our products and services. You can choose not to receive these e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link in any e-mail or by contacting contact@multiplication.com.Certain Multiplication.com content may be hosted and served by third parties. In addition, Multiplication.com may contain links to third-party web sites that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy or data collection practices of any third party.CONTACT INFORMATION:IXL Learning, Inc.777 Mariners Island Blvd., Suite 600San Mateo, CA 94404 (USA)Tel. (650) 372-4040Fax (650) 372-4072help@ixl.com Effective Date: April 30, 2018
© Copyright 2020 IXL Learning All Rights Reserved. Contact Us ×You selected a premium feature. Students Click Hereto return to multiplication.com
Teachers / Parents Click here to learn more about the Premium advantage.Your kids will learn the times tables.
Close
